[Music]
for
last week has been slow slower than I
anticipated but that is important too
settling down along with the season and
preparing for the cold ahead the first
hard Frost has come as well as scattered
snowfall and winter is fast approaching
and we have recently been celebrating
many changes and revelations in our own
lives all welcomed of
[Music]
course
hello it has been a little while this
month has been kind of up and down with
getting my schedule in order so I'm
doing my best and I appreciate your
patience this week and for the
foreseeable future because there have
been uh big changes in my life this
month and so it's been quite exciting
also uh a lot of questions in regards to
making videos and uh YouTube and
everything else about life as well we
recently had the one wonderful news that
we are going to have a baby next year
it's very exciting we are still in the
very early stages so we still have quite
a long way to go many questions many
unknowns hopefully all goes well but yes
since I have of course been quite tired
this month understandably and adjusting
to this new journey ahead I decided it
would just be the easiest to just sit
down and make something a little bit
more simple this week to give me time to
recover a little bit and start out next
week fresh hopefully we have been
wanting to start a family but the timing
was always not quite right but we are
here now and we are just so looking
forward to the months and years ahead of
course already I've noticed that I have
had to make adjustments to life to
productivity to scheduling due to how
I've been feeling and so I have no doubt
that will continue to be an ongoing
Challenge and an opportunity for me to
grow and learn how to surrender and let
go to this new process that does bring
me to a question that has popped up a
lot in the past when I have mentioned uh
Parenthood and starting a family in my
videos it has been from people concerned
about me leaving YouTube due to family
it it changes and the truth of the
answer is I don't know what the future
holds I however am going to do my best
for the foreseeable future to create
videos but I'm sure depending on how I'm
feeling and what we are going through
personally and how the pregnancy is
going I will no doubt be taking more
time to recover and of course to slow
down the process of creating videos that
does not mean I am leaving YouTube of
course I will not be sharing the details
of my journey over the next many months
future children of course will not be
Shing on this channel of course I will
share good news as it comes but it will
not be the focus as a side note as you
know I've been following a desire to
simplify and to be as simple with the
items I have in my home how I am
spending how I'm budgeting all these
things for the Autumn and the holiday
season it has inspired me to be a lot
more mindful about my consumption and
everything that I've been doing even
though we are budgeting and staying very
mindful in preparation for our growing
family I did want to do a couple things
in regards to treating myself and I got
some wonderful opportunities to do that
so I thought I would share that briefly
and of course it has to do with books
and candles I got a couple new books to
enjoy this winter which was extremely
exciting since my birthday is coming up
in a month and so books always seem to
find their way to me this time of year
somehow receiving some new candles C Les
feels like an early birthday present so
um it's definitely been a wonderful
month candles books and news of a baby
so I just couldn't be happier so it's
been it's been really lovely however I
did want to share my two favorite
candles this time of year because I
always do I'm pretty sure I always make
a video about candles just about this
time of year every year so I'm going to
try to keep the tradition going today I
have Hedgehog's knitting Corner which
came in just the cutest little box the
scent is described as Crimson wood and
violet petals I also have owl's Starry
Night feels like a walk through the
winter forest and of course I wanted to
mention that some very good friends of
mine that actually work right next to
the bookstore that I work at have been
making their own candles handmade
candles with essential oils uh directly
from my Valley I will share the scents
and the links down below of the ones
that I really enjoyed in case you were
looking for some candles this time of
year so there you go here's the annual
candle update hopefully um that was a
little less overwhelming than in the
past because in the past I've had a bit
of a problem so we're we're trying to
reel it
back I have been continually spilling
tea on myself throughout this entire
conversation anyway I just wanted to
share the amazing news I am just so
excited for the future but I also want
to let you know that I don't know what
that means for the future of this
channel but we will figure it out one
week at a time and I appreciate your
understanding as I go through this new
Incredible era of life I'm sending you
all some well wishes and I will see you
very soon
[Music]
goodbye